<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AceShiksha</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to AceShiksha</string>
    <string name="tagline">Learn. Play. Grow.</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="student">Student</string>
    <string name="teacher">Teacher</string>
    <string name="select_class">Select Class</string>
    <string name="already_have_account">Already have an account? Login</string>
    <string name="no_account">Don\'t have an account? Register</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">PRIVACY POLICY — ACESHIKSHA\n\nLast Updated: April 13, 2026\nEffective Date: April 13, 2026\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n1. INTRODUCTION\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nWelcome to AceShiksha (\"the App\"), an educational application designed for students in Classes 6–11 and their teachers in Indian schools. AceShiksha is developed and operated by an individual developer (\"we\", \"us\", or \"our\").\n\nThis Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, how we use it, with whom we share it, and what rights you have. By using AceShiksha, you agree to the practices described in this policy.\n\nIf you are a parent or guardian of a child using this App, please read this policy carefully. If you are a teacher or school administrator using this App on behalf of students, you are responsible for obtaining appropriate consents as required by your institution.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n2. WHO THIS APP IS FOR\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nAceShiksha is designed for:\n• Students in Classes 6–11 (approximately ages 11–17)\n• Teachers and educators in Indian schools\n\nThe App may be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 13 without verifiable parental or guardian consent, or without authorization through their school or teacher. If you believe a child under 13 has provided personal data without proper consent, please contact us immediately at nikhilsharma75612@gmail.com and we will delete that data promptly.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n3. INFORMATION WE COLLECT\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\n3.1 Information You Provide Directly\n\nWhen you register an account, we collect:\n• Full name\n• Email address\n• Password (stored in encrypted form via Firebase Authentication — we never see your raw password)\n• Role: Student or Teacher\n• Class level (for students, e.g., Class 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, or 11)\n\n3.2 Information Generated Through App Use\n\nAs you use AceShiksha, we automatically store:\n• Quiz attempts, scores, and answers selected\n• Game scores and attempts (Maze, Car Race, History Timeline)\n• Lesson progress and AI feedback requests\n• Topic interactions and feedback responses\n• Leaderboard ranking data\n• Badges earned\n• PDF content you upload for AI quiz generation (processed in real time and not stored permanently)\n\n3.3 Information We Do NOT Collect\n\nWe do not collect:\n• Your device\'s precise GPS location\n• Photos, camera, or microphone data\n• Contacts or call logs\n• Browsing history outside the App\n• Advertising identifiers\n• Payment or financial information (the App is free)\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n4. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nWe use the information we collect solely to:\n• Create and manage your account\n• Provide personalized learning content appropriate to your class level\n• Generate AI-powered quiz questions and lesson feedback using the Gemini API\n• Display quiz results, game scores, and leaderboards\n• Allow teachers to monitor their students\' progress and performance\n• Generate student progress reports for teachers\n• Maintain and improve App functionality and stability\n• Comply with applicable laws and regulations\n\nWe do not use your data for advertising, profiling for commercial purposes, or any purpose unrelated to the educational function of the App.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n5. AI-POWERED FEATURES (GEMINI API)\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nAceShiksha uses Google\'s Gemini 2.5 Flash API to power:\n• AI lesson feedback and explanations\n• AI-generated quiz questions from PDF content\n• Quiz Battle and Rapid Fire question generation\n\nWhen you use these features, the relevant text or PDF content is sent to Google\'s Gemini API for processing. This is subject to Google\'s own privacy policy and terms of service, available at https://policies.google.com/privacy.\n\nImportant: PDF content you upload for quiz generation is sent to the Gemini API for real-time processing only. We do not store your uploaded PDFs in our database.\n\nYou are using an AI-powered service. AI responses are generated automatically and may occasionally be inaccurate. Always verify important information with your teacher.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n6. FIREBASE SERVICES\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nAceShiksha uses the following Google Firebase services:\n\n• Firebase Authentication: Manages account creation and login. Your password is never stored in plain text.\n• Cloud Firestore: Stores your profile data, quiz attempts, game scores, topics, and progress records. Data is stored in Google\'s asia-south1 (Mumbai) region.\n\nFirebase is operated by Google LLC. Google\'s privacy policy governs Firebase data processing and is available at https://policies.google.com/privacy.\n\nWe do not use Firebase Analytics, Firebase Crashlytics, Firebase Storage, Firebase Cloud Messaging, AdMob, or any other Firebase service beyond Authentication and Firestore.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n7. DATA SHARING AND DISCLOSURE\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nWe do not sell, rent, or trade your personal information.\n\nWe share your data only in the following limited circumstances:\n\n• With Google (Firebase / Gemini): As described in Sections 5 and 6 above, necessary for app operation.\n• With your teacher (within the App): Your quiz scores, game results, and progress reports are visible to the teacher associated with your class within the App. This is a core educational feature.\n• Legal requirements: If required by law, court order, or government authority, we may disclose your information as legally obligated.\n• Safety: If we believe disclosure is necessary to protect the safety of any person or to address fraud or security issues.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n8. DATA RETENTION\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nWe retain your data for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide the App\'s services.\n\nYou may request deletion of your account and all associated data at any time by contacting us at nikhilsharma75612@gmail.com. We will process deletion requests within 30 days.\n\nNote: Deleting your account will permanently remove your profile, quiz history, game scores, and progress data. This action cannot be undone.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n9. DATA SECURITY\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nWe take reasonable steps to protect your information:\n• Passwords are encrypted by Firebase Authentication and never stored in plain text\n• All data transmission between the App and Firebase/Gemini uses HTTPS encryption\n• Firestore security rules restrict data access so users can only access their own records\n• Teacher access is limited to their own students\' data within the App\n\nHowever, no method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your data, we cannot guarantee absolute security.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n10. YOUR RIGHTS\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nYou have the right to:\n• Access the personal data we hold about you\n• Correct inaccurate data (you can update your name and class in the Profile section)\n• Request deletion of your account and all associated data\n• Withdraw consent at any time by discontinuing use of the App\n\nFor any of the above requests, contact us at nikhilsharma75612@gmail.com.\n\nParents and guardians of users under 18 may exercise these rights on behalf of their child.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n11. CHILDREN\'S PRIVACY\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nAceShiksha is an educational app used in school settings. Some users may be under 13 years of age. We take the following measures to protect younger users:\n\n• The App contains no advertisements\n• The App does not allow public posting or sharing of content outside the teacher-student relationship\n• We do not collect more data than is necessary for the educational purpose\n• Student data is only visible to their associated teacher within the App, not to other students\n• We do not use student data for any commercial purpose\n\nIf you are a parent or guardian and you believe your child under 13 has registered without your consent, please contact us at nikhilsharma75612@gmail.com and we will delete the account immediately.\n\nSchools and teachers using AceShiksha are responsible for ensuring they have appropriate authorization from parents/guardians before registering students.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n12. PERMISSIONS USED BY THE APP\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nAceShiksha requests only the following device permissions:\n• Internet access: Required to connect to Firebase and the Gemini API\n• Read external storage (Android 9 and below) / Read media documents (Android 10+): Required only when you choose to upload a PDF for quiz generation\n\nThe App does not request access to your camera, microphone, contacts, location, or any other sensitive device capability.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n13. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make significant changes, we will update the \"Last Updated\" date at the top of this policy. We encourage you to review this policy periodically.\n\nContinued use of AceShiksha after changes are posted constitutes your acceptance of the updated policy.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n14. GOVERNING LAW\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nThis Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of India, including the Information Technology Act, 2000, the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011, and the Digital Personal Data Protection Act, 2023 (DPDPA) to the extent applicable.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n15. CONTACT US\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nIf you have any questions, concerns, or requests regarding this Privacy Policy or your data, please contact:\n\nAceShiksha Developer\n\nDeveloper Name: Nikhil Kumar\nDeveloper Email: nikhilsharma75612@gmail.com\n\nWe aim to respond to all privacy-related queries within 7 business days.</string>

</resources>




